(Leonard:)And how could a chimp
even solve that?
(Leonard:)That was impossible.
(Penny:)Really? You couldn't get it out?
(Barry:)Thank you.
AMY: Wow, the
store looks great.
(Leonard:)So you guys were
testing us both?
(Leonard:)What is the
matter with you?
PENNY: Eh, what's
the matter with them is
(Penny:)they think they're so smart
they don't care
(Penny:)if they hurt
other people's feelings.
(Sheldon:)Sounds like us.
That's not true.
(Sheldon:)I still don't understand
why you're upset.
(Sheldon:)You solved every puzzle faster
than all of the chimps.
(Amy:)Well, except Barnabas,
but he was on Adderall.
(Howard:)I'm sorry, but it's
making me crazy.
(Bernadette:)Can you please
just let it go?
(Sheldon:)Oh, I can help
you with that.
(Penny:)Imagine you're holding
an ordinary pen.
While your favorite pen is
safe and secure in your pocket.
(cell phone rings)
(Howard:)Hold that thought.
(Howard:)Hello?
(Amy:)How can I make this up
to you?